剧情回顾...
Previously on Lost...
噢  该死
Damn it!
-你没事吧  伙计?   -我很好  我没事
-You all right, brother?   -I'm fine. I'm fine.
-我在训练  -为了什么训练?
-I'm training.  -You're training for what?
为了一个环球赛跑
For a race around the world.
-我是Jack   -我是Desmond
-Jack  -I'm Desmond
那么我们在新生活中再见了
See you in another life.
仔细按我说的输入  听懂了么? 不能有一点差错
Type in exactly what I tell you, understand? Nothing else.
4...
8...
15...
16...
23...
42...
现在按"执行"键
Now press "Execute".
-会发生什么事?    -快按
-What's gonna happen?    -Just push it!
Kate!   Locke!
那是谁?
Who the hell is that?
快滚  不然我杀了他
Move and I kill him.
Michael     Sawyer
Jin
其他人  其他人
Others! Others!
-什么?    -其他人
-What?    -Others.
我的孩子在哪儿?
Where's my boy?
嘿  你们把我的孩子怎么了?
Hey, what did you do with my boy?
你听到没?
You hear me?
回来
Come back here!
你想让他死吗?
Do you want him to die?
把枪放下
Put it down.
这就是你所说的吗  Locke?
Is this what you were talking about, Locke?
这就是你的命运吗?
Is this your destiny?
该发生的还是会发生的
"All roads lead here".
这星期我妈又偷了我的钱
My mother stole again from me this week.
我现在都不把钱放在钱包里了 我一直把钱藏着
I don't even keep money in my purseanymore, I've been hiding it.
但她一要喝酒...
But when she wants a drink...
就偷了我30块
She stole 30 dollars.
我知道这对于你们其中的一些人来说不算什么
I know it may not seem like a lot of money to some of you,
但对于我来说却是一个大数目
but it's a lot to me.
我想要回我的钱
And I want it back.
你有什么要说的吗?
Something you want to say?
John  你来这儿已经一个月了...
John, you've been coming here for a month now...
我觉得30块钱不值得你这么大惊小怪
I just don't think 30 dollars is worth getting angry about.
Francine觉得30块...
Francine feels 30 dollars...
是Francine想得太多了
Francine feels a little too much, if you ask me.
你们都是
You all do.
我是很认真的
I mean, seriously...
"他再也没给我回电话" "我妈偷了我30块"
"So-and-so never called me back." "My mother stole 30 dollars."
我甚至都不知道自己父母是谁
I never even knew who my parents were.
几年前  我的...我的亲生母亲找到了我  然后...
Couple years ago, my birth mother found me.And...
她告诉我...
she told me...
我很特别
I was special.
并且...并且她带我去见了我的亲生父亲
And...and through her I met my real father.
好消息  不是么?
Great news, right?
他假装很爱我  为的就是
he pretended to love me, just long enough
从我这里骗走我的肾 因为他需要一个肾来做移植
to steal my kidney, because he had to have a transplant.
然后他把我像垃圾一样丢了出来
And then he dropped me back in the world like a piece of trash,
就像我刚出生时他丢了我那样
just like he did on the day that I was born.
你想要回你那该死的30块 我想要回我的肾
You want your damn 30 dollars back. I want my kidney back!
这也许是件好事
Probably a good idea.
你知道  要是你得了肾癌 你只会有一个肾得癌
You know if you get kidney cancer, you've only got one.
真的很有趣
That's funny.
如果这次聚会被我搞砸了我很抱歉
I'm sorry if I ruined your meeting.
哦  去它的  你只是讲出了 我在那儿一直想说的话
Oh, hell. You just said everything I've always wanted to say in there.
很多时候  我都想站起来大声喊
Most of the time, I want to stand up and scream.
"把那些事都忘了吧  笨蛋"
"Get over it, freaks!"
那你干嘛不这样做呢?
Well, why don't you?
我还是忍忍吧
I have to keep a cork in.
我要是一激动起来是很难停下来的
Once I get all hot and bothered, there's no stopping me.
我想你下周不会来了吧?
Guess you won't be coming back next week?
-是的  我不会来了  -噢  那太可惜了
-No, not likely.  -That's too bad.
我喜欢秃顶的男人
I like bald guys.
-我还没秃顶呢  -我可以等
-I'm not bald.  -I can wait.
呃  顺便说一声  我叫...我叫Helen
I'm...I'm Helen, by the way.
你好  Helen  我是John
Hi, Helen.  I'm John.
Kate在哪儿?
Where's Kate?
把枪放下  不然我崩了他的脑袋
Lower your gun or I'll blow his damned head off.
Kate在哪儿?
Where's Kate?
把枪放下
Put it down.
我什么也不放
I'm not putting down anything!
冷静点  没事的
Jack, calm down. It's OK.
-不许动  -不  不要...
-Do not move!  -Don't...
-不要什么?  -他没有武器
-Don't what?  -He's unarmed...
他刚刚还用枪指着你的头
He just had a gun pointed at your head!
你都干了什么?
What did you do?
我们都会死的
We're all gonna die.
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对： 雯雯  七色九天
后期：xyz 双语制作：胖丫头
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
我得把它修好
I have to fix it.
他到底在说什么?
What the hell's he talking about
如果你不让我起来  我们都会死的
If you do not let me up, we are going to die.
别动  不然我要你好看...
Stop moving, or I swear to God...
你看墙上
Look at the wall!
看到了吗?
You see that?
那是个计时器  一直在倒数计时
That's a timer and it's counting down.
我得输入密码并且按下按键
I've got to enter the code, got to push the button.
不然会怎么样?
Or what?
-Jack  你还是让他起来吧  -不用告诉我该怎么做
-Jack, let him up.   -Don't tell me what to do.
不然会怎样?
Or what?
会发生什么?
What's going to happen?
我们见过面吗?
Do I know you?
你看着他
You got him?
混蛋
Bastard!
怎么了?
What?
没什么  Jack
Nothing, Jack.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
你去哪儿了?
Where are you going?
没有  我...
Nowhere. I...
我...
I...
我只是不习惯睡在其它床上
just have trouble sleeping in a strange bed.
不  这...这和你没关系  Helen  我保证
It has nothing to do with you, Helen.I promise.
我真的很喜欢你
I really like you.
我很抱歉  回头给你电话
I'm sorry, I'll call you later.
早上好啊
Morning.
早上好
John  我知道你喜欢在我家附近开车转悠
John, I know you like to drive through my neighbourhood.
也知道你常常把车停在我家前面
And I know that every now and then, you like to park outside my house.
我本以为我搬了家你就不会来了 但是...你又来了
I thought it might all stop when I moved, but here you are.
我得承认  开始我是觉得挺有意思的
I'll admit, at first I thought it was funny.
但是现在这让我烦透了
Now it's just annoying.
你还是告诉我你到底想要什么吧?
So how about you tell me what the hell it is you want.
为什么?
Why?
什么?
Excuse me?
为什么?
Why?
没有为什么
There is no "why".
你以为你是第一个被我玩弄在股掌间的么?
You think you're the first person that ever got conned?
你需要一个象征性的父亲而我需要一个肾
You needed a father figure and I needed a kidney.
事情就这么发生了
And that's what happened.
忘了它吧
Get over it.
还有John  别再来了
And, John, don't come back.
这儿不欢迎你
You're not wanted.
没必要用枪了  Kate
I don't think you need that, Kate.
你在找什么  也许我能帮上忙
Whatever you're looking for,maybe I can help.
你会修电脑吗?
Can you fix a computer?
那你就帮不了我了
Then you can't help me.
Sayid会修电脑
Sayid can fix a computer.
把他叫来
Get him.
去把Sayid叫来
Go and get Sayid.
你能顺着那根绳子爬回去吗?
Can you get back up that rope?
不用了  这里肯定还有个门
There's got to be a front door here.
在走廊尽头左转处
Down the corridor to the left.
用点力  把手很紧
Be persistent, the wheel sticks.
找到了
Got ya!
现在你得告诉我到底是怎么回事
Now, tell me what's going on.
Jack  我们没时间...
We don't have time...
-我们先停一会儿  -求你了  让我...
-We're taking a time-out.  -Please, just let me...
听着  如果你想继续做你的事 就先告诉我你怎么来到这儿的
You wanna get to work? Tell me how you got here.
是三年前了
It was three years ago.
我参加一个单人环球比赛时
I was on a solo race around the world,
船撞上了暗礁  然后Kelvin出现了
and my boat crashed into the reef and Kelvin came.
是Kelvin  他从丛林中跑了出来
Kelvin   He comes runnin' out the jungle,
"快点  快点  跟我来"
"Hurry! Hurry! Come with me!"
他把我带到这里
He brings me down here.
当时这个已经开始嘟嘟倒计时了 他做的第一件事就是
First thing he does, cos it's beeping,
输入密码  按下按键  声音就停了
he types in the code, pushes the button and it stops.
我问他"到底是怎么回事?"
"What was all that about?" I say.
他回答说"是在拯救世界"
"Just saving the world", he says.
拯救世界?
"Saving the world?"
是他说的
His words, not mine.
所以我也开始这么做了
So I started pushing the button too.
我们一起拯救世界的那段日子还不错
And we saved the world together for a while, and that was lovely.
然后Kelvin死了所以现在就我一个人了
Then Kelvin died. And now here I am all alone.
讲完了
The end!
你不会相信他的话吧 这太难以理解了
Don't tell me you believe this. This is crazy.
你觉得那可能吗  按个按钮就可以拯救世界?
You think that makes sense? Pushing a button?
你就那么相信他的话?
You're going to take his word for it?
我们也只能听他的了  Jack
His word is all we have, Jack.
你没必要只听我的话
You don't have to take my word for it.
看看影片吧
Watch the film.
什么?
What?
书架的最上层  《压力》那本书后面
The bookcase. Top shelf.Behind Turn of The Screw.
放映机在食品室
Projector's in the pantry.
等等
Here...
伙计  我说
Dude, I gotta say,
我还以为我们撑不过昨晚呢
I didn't think we were gonna get through the night.
而且那个婴儿被偷时我还不在场
And I wasn't even here for that baby-stealing part.
我能肯定的告诉你那件事很精彩
I can assure you it was very exciting.
事情也该是时候变得正常了
Things are finally returning to normalness.
Sayid
噢  见鬼
Aw,  crap.
Sayid...
我们需要你的帮忙
We need your help.
你知道些什么?他们对你做了什么?
What do you know? What'd they do to you?
他们到底是谁?
Who the hell are they?
其他人
Others!
你看到Walt了吗?
Did you see Walt?
其他人...有多少?
The Others? How many?
他们有多少人?
How many?
他们蒙住了他的眼睛
They had him blindfolded. Blindfolded.
他们可能有上百人
Could be a hundred of them out there!
-把我推上去  -什么?
-Push me up.  -What?
推我上去
Push me up.
我试试看能不能出去
I wanna try and get us outta here.
来吧  帮帮忙  伙计
C'mon, help us out, Chewie.
有东西压着
They got it weighted down with something.
并且在哪儿被打结固定了
It's tied off somewhere.
加油  把我举高点
Come on, lift me higher.
是个女的
It's a girl.
能告诉我在我下来前这儿发生了什么么  John?
Wanna tell me what was going on down here before I showed up,John?
Kate被绑了起来  Desmond拿着枪指着我
Kate was tied up. Desmond had a gun on me.
我想基本上你已经知道个大概了
I think you caught the gist of it.
Desmond
他想知道我们很多事
He wanted to know a lot about us.
我们是怎么来的  我们是否病了
How we got here. If we were sick.
你没有问过有关他的事?
You didn't ask anything about him?
他拿着枪啊
He was the one with the gun.
你还真沉得住气
You seem calm
作为一个相信世界会在45分钟后毁灭的人来说
for someone who believes the world's going to end in 45 minutes.
他会修好的
He'll fix it.
你明白他说的,这是...
You understand that what he's saying,
这是疯狂的  是不可能的
it's insane. It's impossible.
为什么是疯狂的呢?
Why is it insane?
因为我上次看到那台能拯救世界的电脑时
The last time I saw the computer that would save the world,
感觉并不是现在这样的
it didn't look like that.
你这么心神不安是因为他说他认识你么?
Is the reason you're so upset because he said he recognised you?
因为那才是不可能的
Because that would be impossible.
欢迎观赏  我是Marvin Candle博士
Welcome. I'm Dr Marvin Candle,
这是专为达摩启动计划
and this is the orientation film
第3站制作的影片
for Station Three of the Dharma Initiative.
接下来
In a moment,
我们会对你和你的伙伴做个简要说明
you'll be given a simple set of instructions for how you and your partner
针对你们如何担负起这个岗位的责任
will fulfil the responsibilities associated with this station.
但是首先  还是先来看看历史介绍吧
But first, a little history.
达摩启动计划是1970年首创的
The Dharma Initiative was created in 1970
是Gerald和Karen Degroot智慧的结晶
and is the brainchild of Gerald and Karen DeGroot,
他们是密西根大学两位博士候选人
two doctoral candidates at the University of Michigan.
跟随着比如B.F.Skinner这样的梦想家的脚步
Following in the footsteps of visionaries such as BF Skinner...
他们描绘了一幅大规模的公共研究情景
imagined a large-scale communal research compound
全世界的科学家和自由思想家能够从事研究
scientists and free-thinkers from around the globe could pursue research
在气象学
in meteorology,
心理学
psychology,
超心理学
parapsychology,
动物学
zoology,
电磁学
electromagnetism,
和理想化社会研究方面的发展...丹麦的隐士工业家
and utopian social reclusive Danish industrialist
军需品巨头Alvar Hanso
and munitions magnate Alvar Hanso,
他的强大的经济后盾使得
whose financial backing
他们多目标的社会科学研究设施的梦想得以实现
made their dream of a multi-purpose social science research facility a reality.
你和你的伙伴从现在开始将一直在第3站或"天鹅座"上
You and your partner are currently located in Station Three, or "The Swan",
接下来的540天都将如此
and will be for the next 540 days.
原先的构想是想把第3站建成一个实验室
Station Three was originally constructed as a laboratory
在那科学家们能够研究推测
where scientists could work to understand
这岛上这块区域所发出的单一电磁波
the unique electromagnetic fluctuations emanating from this sector of the island.
但是在实验开始不久之后
Not long after the experiments began, however,
发生了一起...意外
there was...an incident.
从那时开始  下面这些协定就开始被执行了
Since that time, the following protocol has been observed.
每隔108分钟这个按键必须按下
Every 108 minutes, the button must be pushed.
从警报响起的那一刻开始
From the moment the alarm sounds,
你将有4分钟时间
you will have four minutes
把这些代码输入计算机里
to enter the code into the microcomputer processor
使之进入程序
induction into the programme.
当警报响起时  无论你或是你的伙伴必须输入代码
When the alarm sounds, either you or your partner must input the code.
我们强烈建议你和你的伙伴轮流换岗
It is highly recommended that you and your partner take alternating shifts.
这样  你们就会保持时刻警觉地状态...
In this manner, you will both stay as fresh and alert utmost importance
在警报响起时
that when the alarm sounds,
能准确的及时的输入代码
the code be entered correctly and in a timely fashion.
不要尝试拿电脑做任何...
Do not attempt to use the computer for anything...
祝贺你  直到你的替班到达
Congratulations! Until your replacements arrive,
这个计划的未来掌握在你们手上
the future of the project is in your hands.
我代表Degroots
On behalf of the DeGroots,
Alvar Hanso和达摩启动计划的全部人员
Alvar Hanso, and all of us at the Dharma Initiative,
对你们表示感谢
thank you,
(印度合十礼)
namaste,
并...
and
祝你们好运
good luck.
我们还得再看一遍
We're gonna need to watch that again.
那是什么?
What's that?
给你的礼物  我们认识六个月了
It's a present. It's been six months.
有几分像周年纪念  是么?
Sort of an anniversary, right?
-我没给过你什么  -没关系
-I didn't get you anything.  -That's OK.
只花了我一美元
Only cost me a buck.
是我家的钥匙
It's to my place.
我想你大概厌倦了老是敲门
Thought you might be tired of knocking.
呃  Helen...
Well, Helen...
我真不知道该怎么说
I don't know what to say.
只有...一个条件  John
There's just...one condition though, John.
当你来我这儿过夜时
When you stay over,
你就得过夜
you stay over.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我昨晚跟踪你
I followed you last night.
去了你去的那间屋子
To that house that you go to.
是你父亲的房子么?
Is it your father's house?
你为什么跟踪我  Helen? 为什么这么做?
Why would you follow me, Helen? Why would you do that?
你半夜鬼鬼祟祟的出门
You sneak off in the middle of the night.
我只是想知道你去哪儿了  我很在乎你  John
I just needed to know where you were going. I care about you,John...
但是我做什么是我自己的事 是我一个人的事
But what I do is my business. It's personal.
我在愤怒中荒废了我20年的生命
I wasted 20 years of my life being angry.
我告诉自己我得忘了它  但是我...
I told myself I would get over it, but I...
我不能独自面对
I couldn't do it alone.
我需要帮助
I needed to find help.
你帮助了我  John
You help me, John.
现在该我来帮你了
And I can help you.
你只需要向我保证你以后再也不去那个地方了
You just have to promise me that you're not gonna go to that place anymore.
好吧
All right.
好吧?
All right?
你还会再来监视我么?
You're going to watch that again?
你会么?
Aren't you?
不  John  我不会了
No, John. I'm not.
没事  没事
OK, OK!
小姐  你还好吧?
You all right, sister?
-你们是谁?     -我们坠机了
-Who are you?     -We crashed here.
我们本来是在悉尼去洛杉矶的飞机上
We were on a plane. Sydney to Los Angeles...
什么?
What?
我们中有40多个幸存
40 of us made it.
815航班?
Flight 815?
你也是?
You were on it, too?
等等  你是在后舱的么?
What? You were in the back?
它在半空中断裂了  你怎么...
It broke off mid-air, how did you...
我不知道  我不知道  飞机断成了两半
I don't know, I don't know. The plane came apart
有人从我头上冲出来
and somebody's fricking hardside came out of the overhead
把我撞晕了
and knocked me out.
我在水下醒过来  自己游了上来
I woke up underwater and made my way to the top.
游向岸边
Swam to shore.
你这些天全靠你自己活着?
You been out here by yourself all this time?
我试着去找食物
Trying to find food.
一路往前走  希望能找到人
Making my way, hoping to find somebody...
然后  昨天  他们找到了我
And then, yesterday, they found me.
-他们是谁?  -我还等着你告诉我呢
-Who are they?  -You tell me.
你看见一个男孩了么? 10岁  他们带走了我的孩子
Did you see a boy? Ten years old? They took my son.
没有  很抱歉
No. I'm sorry.
我叫Ana Lucia
I'm Ana Lucia.
Sawyer
这是Mike
This is Mike.
这个沉默的韩国人叫Jin
The quiet Korean guy's Jin.
你遇到我们真的是太幸运了
We're about to be the best thing that ever happened to you.
为什么这么说?
How's that?
因为下次那家伙打开笼子的时候
Next time Shaft opens the cage,
他会非常非常吃惊的
he's gonna get a surprising little "howdy-doody".
你联系过那个制作人么?
Are you in contact with the people who made it?
那部影片  你联系过他们么?
The film. Are you in contact with anyone?
如果我联系了你想我还会呆在这儿么?
Do you think I'd be here if I was?
你怎么会不知道坠机的事?
How is it that you didn't know about the crash?
还有我们?
About us?
我每隔108分钟就要按一下键
I push this button every 108 minutes.
我不太出去
I don't get out much.
那么那些接替者...
So these replacements...
Kelvin就是等接替者等死的
Kelvin died waiting for his replacements.
那么你不出去  没看见任何人
So you don't get out, you don't see anyone,
你的食物是哪儿来的?
where's your food come from?
你真的认为事情是这样的么?
You really think this is happening?
为什么不呢?
Why wouldn't it be?
舱门口里面印着"检疫隔离"
It says "Quarantine" on the inside of the hatch
把你封闭在这下面  让你绝得恐慌
to keep you down here, keep you scared.
但是你知道么?
But you know what?
我们在外面已经40多天了  没有人得病
We've been up there for over 40 days and no one's gotten sick.
你认为这只是真实事实的一部份么?
You think this is the only part of it that's true?
你有没有想过可能他们把你困在这儿
Did you ever think they put you here
每隔108分钟去按按键
to push a button every 100 minutes
只是为了看看你是不是真的会去这么做
just to see if you would?
这儿的所有一切...电脑  按键...
That the computer, the button,
只是一个心理游戏  一个实验
it's just a mind game. An experiment.
我每天都这么想过
Every single day.
并且为了我们大家  我希望这不是真的
And for all our sakes, I hope it's not real.
但是影片说这是一个电磁站
But the film says this is an electromagnetic station.
我不知道你是怎么想的 兄弟
And I dunno about you, brother,
但是每次我走过那儿的混凝土墙
but every time I walk past that concrete wall out there,
我都会觉得难受
my fillings hurt.
好了
Right.
不  不
Oh, no!
发生什么事了?
What happened?
一切都完了
It's over.
你是什么意思 "一切都完了"?
What do you mean "It's over"?
你...你在干什么?
What...what are you doing?
你要走了么?
Are you leaving?
Desmond
等等
Wait.
我们可以...我们可以把电脑修好的
We can...we can fix the computer.
Sayid马上就来了  他知道...
Sayid is coming. He knows...
帮我祝他好运
Give him my best.
等等  等等  等等 你去哪儿...
Wait, wait! Where are you...
你不能走
You can't leave!
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
能跑多远跑多远  兄弟
As far as I can run, brother.
-我们该怎么做?  -不用了
-What should we do?  -Nothing.
我们什么都不用做
We do nothing.
这不是真的  没一样东西是真的
It's not real. None of it's real.
这不是...这不是应该发生的事情
No...This isn't what was supposed to happen.
那什么才是应该发生的?
What was supposed to happen?
Jack求你了  别把我丢在这儿
Please! Don't leave me here.
再见  John
Goodbye, John.
-你靠你自己吧  -Jack
-You're on your own.  -Jack.
该死!
Damn it!
怎么会这样?  你想怎样?  你想...
Why is this happening like this? What do you want? What do...
我应该怎么做?
What am I supposed to do?
Helen  你...
Helen, what...
Helen  你...你...
Helen, what..
嘿  Helen  等等
Helen, wait.
Helen
不要
Don't!
Helen
你为什么这么做?
Why are you doing this?
他不会出来的  John  因为他不在乎
He's not coming out of his house because he doesn't care.
我知道你为什么在这儿  为什么你一直来这儿
I know why you're here, why you keep coming here.
你心慌了
You're scared.
你还怕向前...
You're scared of moving forward,
和我一起  和我们一起
with me, with us.
你得来个选择
You're gonna have to choose.
他还是我?
Him or me.
不  不  不  事情没这么简单
No, no. No, it's not that simple.
就这么简单
Yes, it is.
我...我...
I...I...
我不能  我不能
I can't. I can't.
来吧  你可以的  -不  我不能
Yes, you can  -No, I can't!
我不知该怎么做
Because you don't know
因为你不知道会发生什么
what's going to happen.
我们都不知道
None of us do.
这就是我们所说的信念的飞跃  John
That's why it's called a "leap of faith", John.
你不需要一个人面对
You don't have to be alone.
Jack?
Jack
John?
老天...
Dude...
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
John  Jack在哪儿?
John, where's Jack?
Jack走了
Jack's gone.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
是怎么样一个东西?
What does it look like?
是一个断路器  这里肯定有
It's a breaker box. There has to be one.
顺着导线管找
Follow the conduit lines.
行  好的  导线管是什么?
Cool, OK. Great. What's a conduit line?
就是那些管子  沿着他们找
Those tubes. Follow those.
你找到它了么?
Did you find it?
就看你说的"它"是指什么了
Depends what you mean by "it".
好了  我们就这么做
Here's what we do.
Jin假装死了  你喊救命
Jin plays dead. You call for help.
病了的囚犯?  你是认真的?
Sick prisoner? You serious?
那么你有更好的主意了  亲爱的?
What, you got a better idea, sweetheart?
你是怎么拿到枪的?
Where'd you get that gun, anyway?
什么?
What?
那把枪  你怎么在飞机上得到的?
The gun, how'd you get it on the plane?
飞机上有个军官
There was a federal marshal on the plane.
然后呢  你碰巧得到了这把枪?
So, what? You just happened to have his gun?
是的  我很幸运  Mike...
Yeah. I'm lucky. Mike, let's get this thing going.
他们抓你们的时候你为什么不用?
How come you didn't use it when they grabbed you?
当时一直挨着棍子揍
Guess I was too busy getting hit in the face with a club.
你怎么突然这么感兴趣了  小妞?
Why are you suddenly so interested, cupcake?
-嘿  -什么?
-Hey!   -What?
快点  我们开始...我们还得...
Come on, Let's...we gotta...
退后!
Back up!
来人
Coming out.
来人!
Coming out!
怎么了?
What happened?
他们是谁?
Who are they?
停下!
Stop!
哦  对了
Oh, right.
那些数字  是么?
The code, yeah?
什么?
What?
仔细听着
Listen carefully.
如果出现了奇迹 你们把电脑又修好了
If by some miracle you get that computer working again,
你们得输入这些数字 4,8,15,16,23,42
enter the code. 4,8,15,16,23,42
按下"执行"键
Hit "Execute. "
-再说一遍  4  8  15  16...  -闭嘴
-Again. 4,8,15,16...  -Shut up!
什么?
Sorry?
不会有事发生的
Nothing is going to happen.
那些人把你困在下面  给你看一部片子
Some... man takes you down there, shows you a movie,
然后你就凭着信念一个人按那个按键
and you push a button on faith alone?
不会有事发生的
Nothing is going to happen!
是对是错15分钟后就会有结论了  兄弟
In about 15 minutes, you're either gonna be very right or very wrong.
你想向我开枪?  开枪吧 我是不会闲在这儿的
You wanna shoot me? Shoot me. I'm not...
你为什么跑?  你都不知道你到底在躲什么
Why are you running? You don't even know what you're running from!
我记起你了
I remember you.
那次跑步
Running.
我认得你
I know you.
-我见过你  -住口
- I met you.  -Stop.
洛杉矶  我正在训练  对么?
Los Angeles. I was training, yeah?
-你扭伤了你的脚踝  -闭嘴
-You twisted your ankle.  -Stop.
你是一个医生  是么? 有个女孩
You're a doctor, right? There was this girl,
你很为她担心  你说...
you were worried, you said...
你说她的手术失败了
You said you failed her.
-就是你  -这不重要
-That was you.  -It doesn't matter.
-她还好么?  那个女孩?  -这不重要
-Was she OK? The girl?  -It doesn't matter.
-她怎么样了?  -这不重要
-What happened?  -It doesn't matter.
-你怎么能说这不重...        -我娶了她
-How can you say it doesn't...      -I married her!
好的
Right.
那你...
Then, you're...
你不再是他的丈夫了
You're not married to her anymore, then.
那么在新生活中再见了
See you in another life, yeah?
你能修好么?
Can you fix it?
这个人  不管他是谁  换掉了主板
This man, whoever he was, replaced the motherboard.
电源变压器烧了
The power transformer is blown.
你难道不想知道为什么吗?
Don't you need to know why?
我要知道的只是这只计时器在为了什么倒数
All I need to know is that the timer is counting down to something,
并且为什么电脑得尽快修好
and that this computer needs to be repaired.
我肯定在我做完这些后你会告诉我原因的
I'm sure you'll tell me why once I've done so.
找到了
Found it!
那是什么?
What's that?
-Sayid?  -我在继续
-Sayid?  -I'm working on it.
-你得...  -我知道我该怎么做
-You have to...  -I know what I have to do.
重新连接处理器...
Reconnected the processor...
换掉变压器...
Replaced the transformer...
可以了
It's on!
好了  那现在呢?
OK, so what now?
有代码的  他让我输的
There was a code, he made me enter it.
什么代码?
What code?
你能记起是什么数字吗?
Can you remember what it is?
4  8  -等等
4. 8.  -Wait a minute.
15  16  -伙计  我是认真的  停下
15. 16.  -Dude, I'm serious, stop!
Hugo  现在不是时候
Hugo, This is not the time or the place...
是么?  我看是的
Yeh? Well, I think it is!
这是什么? 我们甚至不知道这是干什么用的 我是说我们得...
What is this thing? We don't even know what it does! I mean, we need...
你知道吗?
You know what?
算了  继续吧  该干什么干什么
Forget it. Go ahead. Do your thing.
不是32
It's not 32.
应该是42
It's 42.
他刚和我说的  Desmond
He just told me. Desmond.
最后一个数是42
The last number's 42.
你确定?
You're sure?
是的  确定
Yeah. I'm sure.
你来  Jack
You do it, Jack.
什么?
What?
得你来按
You have to do it.
你自己按  John
You do it yourself, John.
不  你看了影片了  Jack
No, you saw the film, Jack.
这是...这至少是是两个人的工作
This is...this is a two-person job at least.
这个争辩毫无来由
This argument is irrelevant.
Sayid不要  Jack...
Sayid. Don't. Jack.
不要  这不是真的
Don't. It's not real.
听着  如果你想按按键的话你自己按
Look, you want to push the button, do it yourself.
如果这不是真的  那你回来干什么  Jack?
If it's not real,then why are you here?
你为什么回来?
Why did you come back?
怎么就这么难以让你相信呢?
Why do you find it so hard to believe?
-你怎么就这么容易相信呢?   -根本就不容易
-Why do you find it so easy?   -It's never been easy!
你还是按了吧
Maybe you should just do it.
不
No.
只是个按键
It's a button.
我不能一个人这么做  Jack
I can't do this alone, Jack.
我不想这样
I don't want to.
这是信念的飞跃  Jack
It's a leap of faith, Jack.
第一班由我来
I'll take the first shift.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====